

# EMMA BINDI

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **PROFILE**

Enthusiastic, self-starting and dedicated full stack developer.

Currently undertaking a full-time Bootcamp at CoderAcademy in Melbourne, building proficiency in front and back-end programming languages and concepts.

Working in Finance and Procurement requires high attention to detail, excellent time management skills, being adaptable and proficient in software platforms in no time. These years of commercial experience enable my ability to accurately develop code, learn new languages fast, and work effectively in a team.

I take initiative wherever I work, proactively identify problems and opportunities, deliver accurate and complete work fast, and contribute to the culture and people around me.

Outside of that, I am a cheerful and kind individual with strong communication skills, and an energising can-do attitude.

# **EDUCATION**

## **DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 | CoderAcademy (VIC) Awarded "Women in Tech" Scholarship

## **BACHELOR OF COMMERCE: ACCOUNTING**

June 2011 | Curtin University (WA)

## CONNECT

#### **PORTFOLIO**

www.emmabindi.com

### LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/emma-bindi

#### **GITHUB**

github.com/emmabindi

EMAIL | PHONE

emma.bindi@outlook.com | 0404 606 182

# SKILLS

Ruby Rails Git

JavaScript HTML CSS/SASS

## EXPERIENCE

#### **CONTRACT ADMINISTRATOR**

NG Energy

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

- Deliver administration for nationwide solar installation projects. Achieving safety, legislative and reporting compliance
- Championed the setup and roll out of Go Canvas
  Platform, to digitise the extensive library of paper forms

#### **PURCHASING OFFICER**

Shark Bay Salt

Dec 2016 - Jun 2019

- Provision of holistic purchasing and logistics services for remote mine sites, managed competing priorities and customer satisfaction
- Led implementation of automation of administrative tasks
- Member of processes improvement committee
- Contributed to design and testing of Pronto accounting system updates, including forms overhaul in conjunction with IT dept
- Nominated as Pronto SME for support and training activities

#### PROJECT ASSISTANT & FINANCE ALL ROUNDER

BallPoint Construction

Apr 2015 - Dec 2016

- Executed broad range of project support and accounting functions
- Led business through technical transition from MYOB to Xero, including chart of accounts setup & training of iunior clerks

## **TAXATION ACCOUNTANT**

Ernst & Young | Marlston Taxation

2010 - 2015

- Financial reporting and tax compliance for various entity structures including SMSF
- Tax calculations, cashflow forecasting and general ledger reconciliations
- Proven ability to deliver to tight deadlines and display meticulous attention to detail
- Led implementation of new SMSF software (BGL Simple Fund)

## REFERENCES

CHRIS DALMAN Project Director, NG Energy

**ANDREW BARNES** Procurement Manager, Shark Bay Salt